<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sun Yuqi&#39;s Web</title>
    <link>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sun Yuqi&#39;s Web</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/about.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/about.html</guid>
      <description>Skills:
Quantitative analysis including data analysis and visualization, Qualitative analysis and Design-based research.
Proficient in Python, R, Nvivo, Unity, Blender, Photoshop (PS), Premiere (Pr), and After Effects (Ae).
Languages: IELTS:7.0, TEM-8 Level: Good.
Awards:
Champion, United Asian Debate Championship 2022, English as Foreign Language(2022.8)
3rd runner-up &amp;amp; National 1st prize, National English Debating Competition(2021.6)
National 2nd prize, Chinese Collegiate Computing Competition, Information visualization &amp;amp; Graphic Design(2020.7)
2nd prize in Beijing, China Undergraduate Mathematical Contest in Modeling (2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/education.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/education.html</guid>
      <description>Peking University
Instructional Technology(MSc)-Graduate School of Education
Beijing, China, September 2021 - Excepted July 2024
GPA: 3.89/4.0
Courses Taken Frontiers in Instructional Technology (A+)
Educational Games (A+)
Research Methods in Instructional Technology (A+)
Instructional Design (A)
Machine learning in educational research(A)
Big Data in Education (A)
Learning Sciences (A) Beijing Language and Culture University
Digital Media Technology(BEng)-School of Information Science
Beijing, China, September 2017 - July 2021
Average: 85.3/100
Awards Outstanding Graduates Award in 2021</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/portfolio/1sanxingdui.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/portfolio/1sanxingdui.html</guid>
      <description>VR Game Design &amp;ldquo;Divine Tree&amp;rdquo; Based on Sanxingdui Cultural Relics
The digitization of Chinese cultural relics is crucial for preserving information and transforming them into open educational resources. It enables active participation in public science education and promotes the global dissemination of Chinese cultural heritage. Virtual reality game technology has played a significant role in this process, allowing users to experience immersive environments and overcome physical limitations. This study aims to combine the digitization of cultural relics with virtual reality games to provide the public with engaging virtual models, contributing to the popularization and publicity of cultural relics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/portfolio/2appdesign.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/portfolio/2appdesign.html</guid>
      <description>Apps Design Prototype
I have designed two app prototypes and one game prototype, involving user research, prototype development, and interaction design. I am proficient in utilizing Adobe Illustrator and Figma for my design work. I am passionate about creating intuitive and user-friendly digital experiences.
&#34;Solar Terms&#34; Adventure GameExhibitionCreator</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/portfolio/3graphicdesign.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/portfolio/3graphicdesign.html</guid>
      <description>Graphic Design
Poster Designer, Institute of Humanities and Social Sciences, Peking University
Poster Designer, Institute of Economics of Education, Peking University
Poster Designer, Student Union, Beijing Language and Culture University</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/researchexperience.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/researchexperience.html</guid>
      <description>Peking University
Prof. Wenge Guo group, Digital Reading, Learning Analysis Participate in research project of Digital Reading, selected in Digital Humanities Exhibition of Peking University;
Participated in research and practice of construction of new teaching material based on knowledge graph;
Participated in the research about technology integration and toolkits in teaching. Prof. Zhehan Jiang group, Educational Measurement
Participated in the compilation of Chapter 5 Event History Analysis and Survival Analysis, Learning Analysis based on Behavioral Data Sequence;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
