<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Sun Yuqi&#39;s Web</title>
    <link>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/portfolio.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Sun Yuqi&#39;s Web</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/portfolio/1sanxingdui.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/portfolio/1sanxingdui.html</guid>
      <description>VR Game Design &amp;ldquo;Divine Tree&amp;rdquo; Based on Sanxingdui Cultural Relics
The digitization of Chinese cultural relics is crucial for preserving information and transforming them into open educational resources. It enables active participation in public science education and promotes the global dissemination of Chinese cultural heritage. Virtual reality game technology has played a significant role in this process, allowing users to experience immersive environments and overcome physical limitations. This study aims to combine the digitization of cultural relics with virtual reality games to provide the public with engaging virtual models, contributing to the popularization and publicity of cultural relics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/portfolio/2appdesign.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/portfolio/2appdesign.html</guid>
      <description>Apps Design Prototype
I have designed two app prototypes and one game prototype, involving user research, prototype development, and interaction design. I am proficient in utilizing Adobe Illustrator and Figma for my design work. I am passionate about creating intuitive and user-friendly digital experiences.
&#34;Solar Terms&#34; Adventure GameExhibitionCreator</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/portfolio/3graphicdesign.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AmySunyuqi.github.io/en/portfolio/3graphicdesign.html</guid>
      <description>Graphic Design
Poster Designer, Institute of Humanities and Social Sciences, Peking University
Poster Designer, Institute of Economics of Education, Peking University
Poster Designer, Student Union, Beijing Language and Culture University</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
